[
  {
    "question": "The formula \\( \\forall x \\exists y P(x,y) \\rightarrow \\exists q P(q,q) \\) would be treated as a validity",
    "answers": [2],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Under all possible circumstances",
      "By an inference engine that implements occurs check as Skolem functions",
      "By an inference engine that implements occurs check as Skolem constants",
      "Under no possible circumstances"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Universal Instantiation is built on Skolemization.",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Backward Chaining Algorithm can be described as follows:\n<ol>\n<li>i. Pose the original query as a goal.</li>\n<li>ii. Find every clause in the knowledge base whose right-hand side unifies with the goal under some substitution.</li>\n<li>iii. Prove in turn every conjunct on the left-hand sides of each of these clauses, keeping track of the accumulated substitutions.</li>\n</ol>",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "There exists a sentence S in First Order Logic such that S cannot be converted\ninto an inferentially equivalent sentence in Conjunctive Normal Form.",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sentiment analysis is a text classification application.",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The purpose of smoothing is to avoid dramatic effects of low-frequency counts.",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The bag of words model can be seen as a simple language model.",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "‘Freeze’, ‘halt’, ‘cease’ and ‘finish’ are examples of stop words.",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The task of Information Retrieval is to return the answer to a user query.",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Information Extraction systems are often based on templates",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["True", "False"]
  }
]
